yo yo
[Music]
down here on the periscope in the cow be
you hear that terrible noise can you
limit the current to lower than one amp
so it doesn't do that shut off it'll
just lower the voltage right so well my
phone is currently being charged by a
panda connected to a power supply but
it's making a terribly annoying noise
yeah get rid of the one the one is the
problem 800 milliamps that sounds good
there's a charge I've fast
what ok it's drawing 5 volts that's good
I told you what it would do yeah it was
just like all right yes so charges my
phone less fast pelas don't need that
many volts pandas are super reliable it
goes oh that's that's literally a worse
noise that's happy it's oh alright I
don't know no but now it makes noise
could have charged a little bit less we
can check out my panda charging my
iPhone Oh what if we raise the voltage
that's a good idea
yeah pan is getting 16 right don't break
my iPhone man oh oh now we're target
that's good volts that's good didn't
they yeah we changed the power supply to
15 volts now it's showing point 9 so
this power supply at 1 amp ridiculously
turns on its fan and it's loud and
annoying
let's take a look at this panda here see
that pulsing that means it's in fast
charging mode
check out those giraffes buy a giraffe
buy a giraffe today new Honda giraffes
coming in on Monday I think they are
KITT nobody comes with a our kidney oh
it's shitty the new Mac OS X it turns
your eyes into the center yeah yeah yeah
so that's the directions that come with
the Toyota giraffe which harm does do we
support
well not the Odyssey because hard to put
the connector on upside down everyone's
hanger gets the e on board it's a secret
e on board this is on assembly welcome
to Ian's assembly this is thermal grease
just playing with the thermal grease
don't get this stuff on your hands
disgusting sleek normal graceful it's
thermal so these are the prototype Eon
boxes boxes oh they're here
oh you guys too you know you get is like
five minute walk see two hour of Fox all
right so we like put a little potting in
the board this is the fan and USB
assembly they're pretty nice coming
young boards they're gonna be made by us
park these might even be hand assembled
but yeah we'll make sure that we test
him really well the heatsink yeah of
course
this is thermal solutions good to 12
watts
yeah today's a great day I'm gonna
shipping eons now of course I always
have this problem on the periscope
there's a little tripod right b1 all
right let's go over to Andy's desk I'm
sure he doesn't know it's Andy always
does announce we can steal
no no no no guys have you seen the
testing center is the testing center
look at those look at this pant a
testing board Wow nice LEDs on the Panda
testing board he has an e on mounted up
here it's kind of hard to see doesn't
mean there are so we can see what's on
the e on let's take it down right now um
I want that like grippy mount you know
the one that has like the big put in the
rav4 magnet at work you're watching
those insane clown posse videos
yesterday I kinda want to go a Juggalo
convention you know they really do it's
really like such a positive message
yeah well needs that alright um so I
guess I'm just gonna try to do this with
one hand where's ye are number five um
well this is your number one right here
I should be a final production beyond so
let me see if I can wrest this and kind
of see you can see cool um so I can't
obviously see what you're saying yeah so
this this piece here is the fan and USB
assembly just snaps on in like this
we're playing with this snap bit for a
bit so you just
yeah it's cruellest now you guys screws
are terrible it just made it seem like
you could unscrew the back and take it
off really that's really you don't want
to take it off in fact so that's that's
an e on back assembly piece take this
phone sorry guys
Saros
all right is it an icebox
Jamie Foxx all right how about didn't
work so you have to kind of slide the
heat sink it is the bigger guys that's
the bigger box well let's build one of
each and we'll see what we want that
solidly in there making good thermal
conductivity if you have some screws
ready not not the new secret screws for
the new secret stuff yeah only the
oldest Chris don't worry that it was the
new secrets that's not that great this
screwdriver which screwdriver Jim isn't
it we got to work on the flush this
issue this probably would Ilan doing
right now with model trees you know can
you see like what I'm doing yeah no pace
for beet sink there is pace there's
definitely pay that's my pace can't get
12 watts without paste base is essential
yeah if you were to buy a car
specifically for this tell me what the
Civic is a really nice car it has a
torque limit though yeah the Prius was
like gonna be the flagship but the
steering Ricardo complains about it hmm
I'm sure like he says he says that it's
like sticky and then like he's like a
lot of static friction yeah it's just
like a whole the whole column has static
friction I really wonder if that's our
Prius or Prius is in general yeah um
City California
no no it's like you you can see it when
you're just driving like straight in a
parking lot
I'm basically like in order to get the
wheel to turn it has like static
friction that it needs to overcome which
is surprising you'd think I'm like a
tight like a car with like pretty tight
steering like the Prius you wouldn't
have that I do all right
and that folks is a neon so now we don't
touch it
yeah I've reset the Paris really bad hey
hey hey we love periscope ma'am because
it's me right Twitter all right check it
out it turns on we need a we're gonna
need a microfiber cloth
we're gonna make sure every eon is
really nicely polished it won't say
common neil like that wait'll you see oh
man you guys are not gonna show you
we're not going to show you those or not
we're keeping the software I've been
under wraps until Leon chef really this
offers really nice yeah so that's that's
an eel and then we put the EON through
our to our testing procedure we make
sure that everything works squeegees
yeah I got like this to spread the
thermal paste it really is a little tiny
it's not for spreading a thermal paste
on fine look at the size of this thermal
paste Wow
we should thermal paste the world so
that's that's a neon folks let's check
out the boxes is the small one a big one
I agree is this the small one of the -
Yama
we want to make sure that if we bought a
Yeon Panda and giraffe we can put them
all in the same box
hey we got that time I heart stamp
anywhere am I gonna have to like clean
the ink off the stamp when I'm done I
just I'm not good at stamps you guys yes
yeah that's kind of weak do it on this
one terrible I'm not gonna stamps you
guys don't worry George I think we hire
people new better at stamps to me what
we switch W someone else now good good
good we don't solve people we use we
only install people we don't use so yeah
great if anyone's looking to start a web
store Web Store Shopify is where it's at
no it's true really like this is the
thing now Shopify pop-up stores we've
made like like for how for how little
time we've had this store up a naval
forward collision warning toggle right
it's pretty nice you think we want that
I don't know yeah it's cute but you know
alright this front do we have an e on
our thing oh yeah you need to power a
while I really did a bad job look at
what a bad driver did with the stamp
periscope really bad news stamp it's the
same stamp we used on the envelopes in
the pandas videos will come in small
boxes I mean if you buy a panda a
giraffe with the EON we'll put them all
together I think we shipped out the
pandas and the giraffes already yeah
yeah all the secrets of our
manufacturing just an e on a Toyota you
want to admit yeah I want to be able to
fit the truth to write the whole time
[Music]
go back to the huge box yeah I think
this is saying this is war doing yeah I
mean we're gonna wrap it all with
something - yeah yeah this is a nicer
box but you know or we could just put
the EON in this box no we're not
shipping we're not shipping it separate
we'd have to just put of you know we
need we need bubble wrap I like I really
like the size of this box it is really I
really think this box box like look at
that some reason you can't get how large
the other box was I think that's a nicer
bomb there's your box
we gotta fit all the cables and mounts
and stuff six feet enough is that what
you're saying is not enough on the Civic
don't you say any other thing oh it's a
USB two barrel connector that's weird
I got I got it I got it yeah I mean you
know I like things kind of densely
packed right foot pan of cards in here
yeah giraffe cards we have to do it
look at that fold wouldn't you be happy
okay I mean it's that or like to ask the
periscope people do you want the nicer
box or do you want the uh the sticker
well the stamp won't look that bad I'm
just bad at stamping from stole our
periscope people out there what do you
think anything my back button says yeah
that's the small box yeah yeah we got a
small couch get into the custom real
upset small box small boxes where it's
out I know I know right inion all right
you got it to the small box to put eat
your ass see it's a better fit we
absolutely we have some stuff to wrap
the giraffe to right yeah how does your
ass
it's a ban but it doesn't fit if you
shipping with a giraffe yeah I mean I'm
putting this so that and that's what we
can do we package we packages a giraffe
and the Panda separately and then these
are just eons in a box yeah all right we
could fit we can fill all the EON stuff
in the small box - GoPro mounts now and
keeper adjusting it oh watch we should
tell people about that now yeah so we're
including two mounts I'm so these legs
slide into these guys right we're
including two well including two with
you so you can put it two different cars
and we're also including two of these
that have different angles so this is a
20 degree mount meaning this angle is 20
degrees we also included 28 degree mount
for like the wrap floor is a 28 right
yeah 28 yeah have you have a higher car
because you want to make sure the
calibration is within like a reasonable
range you don't want the thing to be
unreasonably calibrated okay well then
at least we can like package up all the
Aeons like separately from and then
you'll just grab one grab we could even
like have like a single pan they're
prepackaged a lot of people just buy one
yes so you'll throw like a tiny Panda
box after a slip they'll continue to
come an envelope like that right you'll
just throw this and the envelope into
like a big table the direct yeah this is
big tie back end looks from us yes
what you're talking about that way
that's just like like it's a thin right
have like inventory right gets keyboard
yes we have a real we have a real scoop
from game again well we can't tell why
we have a real skew for pants cubes or
fans
pandas are real products thankfully I'll
be something nice if we could fit
everything boxes I mean do we need tabs
nicer on the side you kind of do you got
to tape it yeah more money on like their
songs I know suck right madam I hired
engineers instead of packaging people so
nice I mean no it's just what I mean
like we got to do it only the best
reason only the best for the people who
bought a Yong Yong card together tough
so this is what you're not with this
thinking this sharp you won't cross this
out this is not what the stamps gonna
look like you guys it's going good I'm
not good at stamps vanilla gorilla wants
the messed up smaller stamps
that's all right mr. classics dams
that's about lean departure for sugar
for shipper nothing average coming out
for shiver shiver + sugar + shift+ now
we've got a percent battery but I got
time to steep and here
the Vice the phone a device see what
guys advise his data partition increased
on Eon yet will be yeah we're gonna get
the data partition to be big
particularly if you got a 128 kg on
that's that's driving for days I was
surprised but I'm happy we offered it um
there's not too many of those in stock
so don't don't too many people buy the
128 games
could you put shiver Plus on iOS no
shiver plus only runs on eons when do
you ship the comma light on Wow you know
they heard about the secret new sensor
and what if it's a wide are place all
lied all right that's true Joyce is 128
yes let's see the secret guys secret can
we hear sensor name was not the pigeon
it's like I'm like a few boards around
here if you probably like that board
over there at the bottom of that boy
it's at the bottom of the list after the
EON ship yes anka zoom in what's the
sensor first letter l l like you know
else the back of the benzene or how many
aeons will we ship tonight none like
next week it's close what close were
close for close productions hard I'm
lighter to start with Al the llama
remember the Koala do you do we
prototyped koala SoundCloud slash time
cruise up yeah the Edison yeah but what
about the jewel The Jewel yeah the Koala
was gonna have a jewel
I don't know ma'am koalas are extinct
we're really crabby look at how fast
this pan is charging my iPhone I know 10
watts this is charging an iPhone like
twice as fast the real iPhone charging
those are so good
did you write made in America no oh man
I wouldn't do that it is made in America
though it is but what a koala do there's
like a better Panda yeah well this is
just talking our oh yeah I can do
both cameras the same time Marhaba all
right you you guys know that I'm a big
America fan you guys know that I love
America but like I'm not gonna like this
tacky I'm gonna say made in America you
know it's like it's made its quality
right like investigate us or some yeah I
don't want to see that's what I mean
like I don't wanna I just don't want to
be a part in I'm not yeah all the
thermic pace to use is not made in
America yeah there's like stupid
restrictions about it's like non-gmo you
know like it's like it's a completely
like arbitrary distinction then that's
not who we're marketing tonight you know
what I mean yeah you're marketing
because you know you want to brass used
in your metal inserts
Oh does it use the camera to steer the
car so Ian's officially don't drive cars
he owns our dash cams I'm very proud to
be from America you guys know I'm proud
to be from New Jersey that's even that's
even how do you young rear view merit
Thank You chef we're gonna down the rail
adapter we don't include that and we
don't encourage people to do that
so technically yeah if you do that we
can't sell anything that replaces your
rear view mirror because of FMVSS but we
do we do we do give it away if you want
to do it yourself we can't we can't sell
anything or encourage you to do it but
if you want to do it yourself as long as
you're complying with your local laws
which you can you are allowed to remove
the rearview mirror on your car but we
can't sell a product that forces you or
encourages you to remove your rear view
mirror I mean this isn't even like a
Honda we have the rearview mirror but on
the Toyotas we don't we're Schiphol with
these things the GoPro mounts just take
it to your windshield again make sure
that's legal in your state most states
have a fairly reasonable rules about it
if you can't stick it right in front of
your face and it can't take up more than
like a couple square inches but there's
a Honda mirror - GoPro STL file yeah if
anyone does want to convert so yeah you
could just you just print out any 3d
printer yeah it's the one we're using
nothing nothing on windshields in your
state whoo
that's rough could be on ever
unofficially drive the car well the over
pilot does support the Aeon but the Aeon
doesn't officially drive your car it's
not a self-driving car yet it's a dash
cam development kit the key word there
is development so you can develop and if
you want on it what are you gonna make a
HUD Oh everything's about to look a lot
better have you guys seen so check out
the screenshots on leonov shiver shiver
plus nebraska doesn't care yeah
no safer flash no
Yeah right doesn't look good they kind
of come up by one I want to buy anything
it's a good experience it's really look
I don't build these things for like a
market I kind of built the stuff that I
kinda always want it you know it's kind
of and you want ways on your car to is
really what you want I was driving I was
drunk of cars to Thanksgiving I'm in the
Civic and I'm like my phone was uh I
just wanted to like like like my
Mercedes at least had like a decent map
that could stay like wicked acidic one
relax it's not usable BMW 3-series will
at work I mean will it work to do what
will it be a dash cam and a 3-series
yeah uh don't ever code in Java gross
Java is terrible he's Python you know
why cuz it's just print and it used to
just be print with a space but now it's
print with two parenthesis anti Python
three to four life
Civic had map update pushy I don't care
if they update the map like my problem
isn't the map it's the software it's not
like there are roads missing it's like
wow you sound like the Microsoft
connected but yeah no I mean so you guys
know where we're going with this
obviously you're gonna be able to type
in shipper on your phone you're gonna be
able to type in your destination and
I'll get pushed you're right eventually
eventually and that's like like shipper
is kind of you know you can use shipper
as a dash cam it's a way to get into the
ecosystem but it's also gonna kind of be
a remote control for your car to the
point that like if you if you have a
panda maybe you'll be able to like
unlock your car from your phone okay we
can really push a lot of things you
scroll up far enough you said something
silly I can't scroll what's the most
important spec for the e on camera
for modeling resolution uh the camera is
really nice I mean the nice thing about
the camera is more more the way we run
it we've written our own camera stack we
don't use any Qualcomm stuff much more
reliable and it's it's we have we have
like precise timings my timing is really
important whenever you're dealing with
anything that's like quasi real-time
I mean people make fun of us for using
like Python right don't look it up are
those not real time yeah it's like plus
or minus five milliseconds your shutter
on your camera takes fifty milliseconds
to roll right so it's not it's not five
milliseconds here it's 50 milliseconds
but you know that's the kind of thing
that if you're running through some like
post-processing stuff like like you
camera server does its you don't know
why not do a paid app with lane
departure warning yeah selling software
yeah not that interesting you play
pac-man in Park mode she we shipped
games on it's fun is Park OGE on App
Store Android we can we can make it so
you could probably kind of run other
apps if it's not like janky we'll do it
you know I'm not it's not like we're
trying to control the thing you'd like
SS agent do it whatever you want on it
he's kind of it would just kind of want
to I don't like make the experience nice
it's more like working well and then
we're gonna have the e on App Store
reviewers and then we're gonna have to
go through like I don't like the
reviewers at Apple you know what I mean
chrome on yon how about how about be on
in chrome right alright you go to drive
my car dock today
we could probably make it so with with
the Panda Jas library that'll talk to
your panda over JavaScript you could
drive your car right from a web browser
that'd be kinda nice
all right guys uh I can you know never
receive button presses from a car wheel
yeah so the Toyota is unfortunately
hardwired a lot of them but on the Civic
we can get almost all of them I don't
know what Marhaba means or monthly
subscription yeah again maybe maybe oh
no it's not that exciting to me you know
what's exciting to me winning
self-driving cars no forward collision
warning day one on on on eons with
shiver plus assuming you have a
supported car you need a radar for it
but we're gonna ship vision only forward
collision warning and chef applause and
we're gonna ship lane departure warning
and here's the thing about lane
departure warning right um
so forward collision warning is a lot in
some ways easier to do than lane
departure warning most people turn off
lane departure warning in their car
because they're really terribly done so
if we do it it's gonna be really good
our forward collision warning no know
what you're flying cars we're working on
we're working on mesh 3d we're moving
everything like all our mapping stuff is
in 3d so it'll work good with flying
cars because cars kind of fly I mean
they just fly along the road right like
the road change out to lane departure
warning most people turn it off and in
two thirds of people turn it off in
their cars because there's too many
false positives when you have a warning
system false positives are super
annoying because I mean it's the boy who
cried wolf right maybe not maybe not um
maybe because the person is doing good
job modeling with your head either yeah
I mean we really want to you know the
boy who cried wolf is a story of false
positives like false positive torque
moments no I like my to know like my
pork limits Oh like false positive
torque limits like when it says turn too
sharp yes oh yeah
we can can do better on that we can we
can certainly not we can change how we
show that alert we show the alert now
whenever we're at max torque of the
steering wheel but sometimes max torque
is so close to the right steering angle
we could not show that alert yeah we
should do that because you paid a I
Drive assist app yeah what and then I'm
gonna like like cell like engagement and
stuff I'm gonna like oh man look we're
selling like red light DLC my dollars
red lights five dollars have you know do
that if I like really wanted to go
full-on troll I'm sure the VCS would
love me what are my thoughts on necks
are it's alright do we buy or do we all
we have one oh let's take a look a sense
of pride and accomplishment winning self
dragon cars that's really what I want to
do will advance torque limit warnings
come with Maps yeah we can do we can do
a lot more with the Tarpan mornings with
maps and we can like this is next hours
little camera that they ship so yeah you
know don't have 3m VHB 'ls you know the
joke about access camera right yeah yeah
they like bought some like Chinese
knockoff camera and called it like necks
are cab this isn't like exciting for me
right like for us shiver is a starting
point not an ending point shiver is the
way people almost everyone who's bought
and Beyond from us and everyone who
who's in our ecosystem started with
shiver right shiver is the beginning
point to a self-driving car I mean it
will get better eventually all the
features will trickle down but in 2018
if you're gonna want their really nice
warnings you gotta buy any on just
because we can do a lot more with the
power its power eventually I feel so
good the next gen i phone accesses
iphone Exadata are good enough to
probably arrive some sudden drive is
this thing what $600 instead for a
monthly subscription to what
Mobile is a monthly subscription do that
$6 for yes your put 0.2 when I move at
least this week I have a model we got a
qualified that's what I've been working
on all weekend I've been working on
models so zero point three point I will
definitely come out this week there's
some chance didn't want to model the
breaking is the ring is good controls to
do the job with that
alright guys thanks for joining me
bye bye Young's shop like I'm sorry
bye cool